{
  "study": [
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "potato",
      "answer": "la pomme de terre",
      "attempt_count": 6,
      "correct_count": 5,
      "date_created": "2023-04-22 01:19:18.291388+00",
      "tags": [{ "id": 3, "tag_name": "food" }]
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "ice cream",
      "answer": "la glace",
      "attempt_count": 6,
      "correct_count": 4,
      "date_created": "2023-04-22 03:11:15.170146+00",
      "tags": [{ "id": 3, "tag_name": "food" }]
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "apple",
      "answer": "la pomme",
      "attempt_count": 6,
      "correct_count": 2,
      "date_created": "2023-04-22 00:23:34.377421+00",
      "tags": [{ "id": 3, "tag_name": "food" }]
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "cake",
      "answer": "le gâteau",
      "attempt_count": 6,
      "correct_count": 5,
      "date_created": "2023-04-22 01:20:33.534491+00",
      "tags": [{ "id": 3, "tag_name": "food" }]
    }
  ],
  "user": {
    "decks": [1],
    "tags": [{ "id": 3, "tag_name": "food" }]
  },
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "deck_name": "French ",
      "card_count": 16,
      "tags": [
        { "id": 1, "tag_name": "places" },
        { "id": 2, "tag_name": "family" },
        { "id": 3, "tag_name": "food" },
        { "id": 4, "tag_name": "travel" }
      ],
      "cards": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "house",
          "answer": "la maison",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 5,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 01:09:20.13869+00",
          "tags": [{ "id": 1, "tag_name": "places" }]
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "potato",
          "answer": "la pomme de terre",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 5,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 01:19:18.291388+00",
          "tags": [{ "id": 3, "tag_name": "food" }]
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "question": "paper",
          "answer": "le papier",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 3,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 01:08:22.76537+00"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "menu",
          "answer": "le menu",
          "attempt_count": 5,
          "correct_count": 5,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 22:47:02.51375+00"
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "ice cream",
          "answer": "la glace",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 4,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 03:11:15.170146+00",
          "tags": [{ "id": 3, "tag_name": "food" }]
        },
        {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "sea",
          "answer": "la mer",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 1,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 22:17:42.223858+00",
          "tags": [{ "id": 1, "tag_name": "places" }]
        },
        {
          "id": 7,
          "question": "chair",
          "answer": "la chaise",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 1,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 01:22:08.61725+00"
        },
        {
          "id": 8,
          "question": "water",
          "answer": "l' eau (f.)",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 3,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 01:13:22.661077+00"
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "question": "flower",
          "answer": "la fleur",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 4,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 01:21:33.973047+00"
        },
        {
          "id": 10,
          "question": "bed",
          "answer": "le lit",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 4,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 01:16:42.129703+00"
        },
        {
          "id": 11,
          "question": "apple",
          "answer": "la pomme",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 2,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 00:23:34.377421+00",
          "tags": [{ "id": 3, "tag_name": "food" }]
        },
        {
          "id": 12,
          "question": "sister",
          "answer": "la sœur",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 3,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 00:36:37.606332+00",
          "tags": [{ "id": 2, "tag_name": "family" }]
        },
        {
          "id": 13,
          "question": "car",
          "answer": "la voiture",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 4,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 01:10:04.891455+00",
          "tags": [{ "id": 4, "tag_name": "travel" }]
        },
        {
          "id": 14,
          "question": "A round trip ticket to Paris, please.",
          "answer": "Un billet aller-retour pour Paris, s'il vous plaît.",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 2,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 01:38:00.775623+00",
          "tags": [{ "id": 4, "tag_name": "travel" }]
        },
        {
          "id": 15,
          "question": "mother",
          "answer": "la mère",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 5,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 00:39:05.571537+00",
          "tags": [{ "id": 2, "tag_name": "family" }]
        },
        {
          "id": 16,
          "question": "cake",
          "answer": "le gâteau",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 5,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 01:20:33.534491+00",
          "tags": [{ "id": 3, "tag_name": "food" }]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "deck_name": "Spanish ",
      "card_count": 5,
      "tags": [
        { "id": 11, "tag_name": "time" },
        { "id": 12, "tag_name": "greetings" }
      ],
      "cards": [
        {
          "id": 17,
          "question": "year",
          "answer": "año (n) masc",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 5,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 00:39:05.571537+00",
          "tags": [{ "id": 11, "tag_name": "time" }]
        },
        {
          "id": 18,
          "question": "calendar",
          "answer": "calendario (n) masc",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 5,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 00:39:05.571537+00",
          "tags": [{ "id": 11, "tag_name": "time" }]
        },
        {
          "id": 19,
          "question": "Hello",
          "answer": "Hola",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 5,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 00:39:05.571537+00",
          "tags": [{ "id": 12, "tag_name": "greetings" }]
        },
        {
          "id": 20,
          "question": "Good evening",
          "answer": "Buenas noches",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 5,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 00:39:05.571537+00",
          "tags": [{ "id": 12, "tag_name": "greetings" }]
        },
        {
          "id": 21,
          "question": "Good morning",
          "answer": "Buenos días",
          "attempt_count": 6,
          "correct_count": 5,
          "date_created": "2023-04-22 00:39:05.571537+00",
          "tags": [{ "id": 12, "tag_name": "greetings" }]
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
